all right so I want to welcome you guys
to my brand new 2 million dollar house
that I just moved into so let's get it
all right so welcome to my brand new
house we got three take profits in this
house we gotta take profit one take
profit two and then we got the rooftop
so let me give you guys a full tour so
it's crazy because I came from living in
a super small house like this big to
living and uh okay nice like apartment
and I moved into this mega mansion by
myself which like every single day it's
feeling bigger and bigger so first thing
first we got a Christmas tree
um this year I wasn't focused too much
on Christmas I was focused more on the
whole entire house so we got our little
executive area here
um I don't know I feel like it was
pretty cool because I decided to make
this kind of like a lounge area we got
some nice spinning chairs we got our s
for seven forget
um shout out to our Atlanta gift to me
both of these dope ass art pieces that I
don't know if I'm gonna put exactly how
they are right now because I have a big
big campus coming which probably take up
this whole entire wall so I'll probably
put Kobe right there which I think would
look super dope and then I'll put
Mohammed somewhere upstairs so as you
come over here we got our dining table
so this dining table is probably like
one of the most expensive pieces in this
whole entire area and you can't even
tell like I've been living here for two
weeks and I haven't even ate at this
table once we got the little bear which
kind of matches the hood of my Lambo so
I got my car painted on a live uh art
show and then he gave me the berry to
match
um let me show you guys the center
forget garage so this is the garage so
this is going to be like my man cave
more or less so right now as you can
tell it's working across if you try
putting up the dartboard didn't work out
that good
um we got some built hexagon lights in
here it's gonna be like my man cave I'm
probably gonna put the lounge here we'll
put a big TV here or probably a
projector and then this is gonna be our
Center forget wall which I feel is like
go we got Center for your merch that I'm
just gonna give to people because I'm
gonna do something for my students for
everybody that is a student of mine you
know I'm gonna fly them all bring it to
my house spend the weekend here with me
and I'm giving the merch I don't want to
sell merch I don't know everybody does
that so I just give it away for free if
anybody's good at ping pong it's not
super nasty
this right here is a real gun it's not
loaded or anything I just have it for
the decoration and stuff um we have our
Winery which funny enough the reason why
it's like all wet down there right now
is because earlier today I just
connected my new Subs in the house and I
was putting the music super loud in the
1942 bottle fell slammed broke and just
completely made a huge mess here uh here
we got our poker room so right now this
is our poker room so these are some
tools we're using earlier to kind of
hang the dartboard but this right now
I'm gonna put some nice uh round chairs
all around the table I'm going to paint
everything in here black as well put a
shell of like just top decorations in
here I'm a really good poker player at
least I think and to me it's like one of
my passions because it teach you like
patience waiting for the right hand
um another bathroom oh by the way I have
seven bathrooms in this whole entire
house so it's a five bedroom uh seven
bathrooms so this is our living area so
right now this is our kitchen I only
have one stool
silly furniture
what's going on I've been waiting two
months for my stools I only there only
probably one stool waiting for my two
other stools uh we got a dope super big
island I personally cook for myself
every single day uh breakfast sometimes
lunch I usually go out to eat lunch just
to get out of the house uh over here we
got our kind of like morning breakfast
table which I do myself every single
morning uh and we got a nice little dope
art piece that I came up with our chill
chair then over here we got probably one
of my favorite things in the whole
entire house which is my massage chair
so like I kid you not I will probably
get on this massage for like two times a
day has zero gravity so it throws you
completely back I've knocked out on here
super dope we got a TV surround system
PS5 that never probably even use I think
that whole entire wall right there I'm
gonna put a uh like brick you know like
wallpaper that is like fake brick or am
I making like a cool design because I
don't want to put too many things on the
wall because then they're kind of just
like fight against each other so I'm
just gonna make that one full wallpaper
which will look dope now we got the
backyard
so we have our pretty nice sized pool we
got our barbecue downstairs we have
another barbecue upstairs just to have
kind of both nice little lunch table to
have outside here I love the way this
house is displayed because I don't
really ever get sun on this part of the
house so you're able to enjoy backyard
we're not having that huge heat of Miami
hitting you all the time right so you
got the heater working right now because
we're in December might not be that cold
but the water's still gets super cold so
you got the heater working right now um
some decorations I got some nice things
coming in here you see how there's Turf
on this piece right now I'm gonna put
Turf on all of this section here and
turf throughout all of that stuff but
that's like something that probably
gonna do maybe in two three weeks I just
literally like two weeks or two weeks
all right so now I want to show you guys
my master bedroom office media room this
is take profit two of that let me just
let me just show you guys all right so
first thing you see when you go upstairs
is super Comfy Couch kind of just like
chill Lounge area
um now we got we got the most important
room of the house the set and forget
obviously all right so first thing
you've seen you come in we have these
super bright hexagon lights so this is
super dope I painted the roof black so
when you turn on the lights it gives it
a dope contrast
um we have the same training setup as we
had before I love this setup because
every single screen is for something
specific we got our uh camera TV system
pretty much I just see the cameras of
the house just rolling all day feels
dope you got our balcony to the outside
the balcony to the outside you can
pretty much just Overlook the cars while
you're trading just take a little break
come out here get some wind
but I'm out of breath in the state
so yeah since where I come I'll go look
at the cars by the way got a new car
coming soon very very soon I already
bought it I'm just waiting for it to
pull up I bought it out of state just on
the way so I'm probably gonna put here
one of those little like cocoon chairs
so it looks pretty comfy cozy out here
in the balcony
um when you come in that is our bathroom
so pretty much I'll go from Trading take
a dump trading take a dump trading
ticket no okay okay all right so then we
got TV right here so I just played some
stuff around me
this is probably one of the most
interesting things of the whole entire
house thinking out the first thing that
I did when I moved into the house I just
put this on the wall and as I'm like
moving like three four days that I
settled in I realized that the light is
shining right on this poster it's right
in the middle and it literally says give
everything I don't know if that means
something or if it's a sign but this
shows you what is possible you literally
give everything that you got so I even
get goosebumps sometimes when I see but
like I feel that stuff so our next room
is our thinking room so if you guys
don't know
giveaway at 75 000 so subscribe just hit
the Subscribe button it's on one of
these
so I'll come in here with the boys uh
we'll just chart up some stuff we
literally just think of some ideas of
what to tell you to do while trading
content whatever the case is every room
has its own bathroom so it's a pretty
dope room so this is going to be a room
media slash office for my students so
whenever students come to my house I'm
just going to put them in here in their
own desk by the way if you guys aren't a
student of mine I probably only have
about 150 students because I keep it
very close to a certain amount of people
on 111 2023 I'm going to open the guided
boot camp again if you guys see all
these comments right here everybody's
talking about the golden video my golden
video gives you everything about my
trading plan of full checklist on how to
properly scalp day trade and swing trade
I don't actively trade every single way
but my strategy gives you the proper
checklist on how to trade every single
week in my chat I have scalpers day
Traders swing Traders I even have some
of the traders that help me catch
scallops in the chat we just talk
everything about this group you guys
want to know more about that stuff shoot
me a DM or just click the link below but
I'm going to bring students occasionally
to my house uh because this you know
Traders want to meet other Traders I
remember when I was a Trader by myself I
wanted to get to know how to Trader so I
can get some of my students that are
doing dope results or are serious bro I
have no problem bringing you to my house
and you just chill here for a little bit
we'll think of some ideas whatever the
case is next we got
um my master bedroom so like I said
earlier City Furniture is taking forever
for my stuff graph and Stefan or
whatever your name is don't roast my
room right now the things are still
coming I've only been here for two weeks
so this is my master bedroom I pretty
much have a California king and look how
small it looks in this whole entire
space I've got a couch for this section
right here and then I bought a super
super dope art piece that is going to go
in there as well I bought just some
decoration over here
um I bought another massage chair that
I'm gonna put over there I'm just still
like debating I should put it here or
somewhere else I have my TV projector
that I'm gonna put up wanted to put a
cool TV but I think I'll project it
would look cooler the lights as you can
tell we have this little Gap up here so
I'm going to put dope LED lights all
around the top so it can look you know
colorful again still waiting for the
parts to come but we got a dope mirror
come in here like huge mirror pretty
much takes up the whole entire walk so
there's my bathroom I have a TV in my
bathroom because I'll pretty much while
I'm showering here put a music video or
just watch the cameras of the whole
entire house we have a huge shower could
fit like 20 girls in here maybe I don't
know I gotta test it out we got a tub
and if any of you guys know what this is
right here I have no idea what this is
whatever this is please let me know I've
never used it I'm scared to use it and I
don't want to use it unproper so please
inform me what the is that now we
got our closet so I'm not gonna lie when
I move into this closet I was kind of
intimidated because it's just by myself
and I've learned how to divide the
closet so this right here is kind of
like my going out stuff I went out shoes
or going out watches just going out
section this is like chill section which
is pretty empty right I think the stuff
are in the drawers and this is just more
like house stuff like towels stuff
throughout the entire house and I have a
kind of like a circle thing you come
here and then sit so now we're gonna go
to take profit three which is the
Rooftop
so this painting actually right here I
was going to put somewhere around here
which it pretty much means the best
views come from the hardest climbs not
because you just climbed three flight
stairs
and you're out of breath but because it
mean something losing my rooftop um
these are the weights for my gym I just
move them inside because I don't want to
take a rusty outside but with my rooftop
I love this spot it's probably one of
the best Vibes out of the whole entire
house I think it's better to have a
rooftop than having a backyard my
personal preference as of right now so
this is kind of like my tanning chairs
I'll come up here to time and chill for
a little bit
um we got our gym section so there's my
calisthenics I think it's called we do
some pull-up steps and then I bought a
squat squat rack but it's on the way so
still haven't gotten it full squat rack
we got our bench with our mirrors so we
put some mirrors here so you can you
know properly get you know your your
compound or whatever
um just missing for the squat rack we
got a bathroom over here full bathroom
shower
so this is um
I'm there use this actually probably use
it today and then we got our barbecue so
whenever we want to hit a barbecue
upstairs from here so you just pretty
much Grill it eat it over here in this
section and I have this whole entire
huge backyard area here that I have no
idea what to do so again if you guys
have more ideas drop a comment
um I'm 22 years old if I'm able to do
all of this pretty much by myself so
fast literally shows you guys what is
capable from Trading all you have to do
is give it your everything give it your
100 I'm living proof literally that if I
can do it so can you guys there
shouldn't be any excuses to why you're
not doing it and all I have to say is
just send a forget baby see you guys